You're telling me the authority for today's day, second item on the agenda is in the
patient by a pastor of Southern Hills Baptist Church, Hermione, hope is the relative
of the new Miami, and been about here about six months, we appreciate you being here now.
What's good Lord and prayer?
God, we are so grateful, Lord, that Father the work that you're doing in the life of this
community.
God, we have an opportunity to be a part of that, to help make decisions.
Lord, you told us to trust in you, God, we thank you, that on the wall, it commemorates
God that we do trust in you.
You said if we, if we trust in you, God, and we lead not upon our own understanding, God,
if we, that you'll direct our paths and so God, I pray for your guidance and your direction.
And the lives of these men and women, God, who lead this town in this community, I'll
pray for you for the work and ask your hand of guidance upon God.
Thank you for their integrity and their witness and their honesty and their truth, God, as they conduct
your business, God tonight, on behalf of each and every citizen in this town, in Christ name
we pray.
Amen.
Ladies and gentlemen, my apologies to the flag of the United States of America, and to the
Republic of the United States of America, and to the Republic of the United States, one nation
of the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States of the world, thank you.
Thank you.
I remember first, public input and unscheduled personal appearances, we have a very large contingent
in the audience tonight, is there anyone that wishes to address the special utility authority
on any agenda items?
You're being known, item five is considered agenda staff is recommending item six to eight,
if there are no questions, I have a motion please.
Most of you have put in there.
And the second, second, roll call, jump in, four, sir.
All right.
Western.
Number nine is new business team, anything underneath is, not for me you're on it now, okay.
And there's trustee community announcements in the announcements, and that is meeting.
Item 11 is adjourned.
The motion adjourned.
And the second, second.
Roll call.
Western.
All right.
Four, sir.
Johnson.
All right.
I think you will now move right into.